# **BEVERLY L BRASHEAR**

1287 Trapani Cove, #1, Chula Vista, CA 91915 | H: 619-339-8473 | C: 619-339-8473 | blbrashear@gmail.com

# **Experience**

#### **Lead Interface Analyst**

May 2015 to March 2020

#### Prometheus Laboratories - San Diego, CA

- Lead all phases of interface development: consultation, analysis of needs, system analysis, design, programs analysis, programming, QA, debugging and documentation for 20 + customers.
- Create and design HL7 Interfaces using Corepoint Interface Engine (create derivatives, action lists, web service endpoints, database associations, code sets
- Work under HIPAA compliance guidelines for construction of HL7 Interfaces
- Collect and provide technical details about VPN connection for bi-directional HL7 interfaces
- Provide project management for HL7 Integration work projects
- Schedule and facilitate conference calls between internal and external clients specific to HL7 projects
- Design workflow and document process through customer-facing documents
- Work directly with internal customers to properly vet the HL7 process
- Organize plans for testing and go live procedures
- Troubleshoot HL7 interfaces and provide production support to clients
- Facilitate vetting processes for approval of HL7 Interface projects
- Work closely with internal customers, i.e. client services, order processing, and accessioning
- Build and sustain rapport with internal and external clients
- Install Corepoint Interface Engine software and develop various environments (Development, Test and Production)
- Provide assistance to users of the Microsoft Dynamics Great Plains (ERP) software
- Develop working relationships with various software vendors for maintenance and upgrade of critical software
- Maintain ICD Codes for clinical purposes
- Maintain organization chart through People Fluent product "Org Publisher"
- Document network configurations of interfaces
- Update and work through processes in StarLIMS (clinical studies data application
- Provide project management for StarLIMS enhancements and changes
- Research and troubleshoot issues with proprietary LIMS
- Documentation of current work projects in Workfront
- Experience with BizTalk for HL7 connections
- SQL Server database maintenance
- Protect company reputation and build loyal client base by working relentlessly to resolve problems and improve customer satisfaction
- Supported internal stakeholders in operational improvements and resolution of software problems to deliver top-notch customer service
- · Planned and executed decommissioning major network servers
- Successfully led key projects which resulted in adding more clients to existing client base
- Proactively identified and solved complex problems impacting operations management and business direction
- Write scopes, requirements for various information technology projects

- Deliver an exceptional level of service to each customer by listening to concerns and answering questions
- Create communication strategies to meet client objectives
- Exceptional attendance record with special attention to punctuality and preparation to work upon arrival
- Write agendas and notes and sent out automatic notifications for upcoming meetings
- Oversee various HL7 and other department related projects from conceptualization to completion

## Interface Developer

Jul 2012 to May 2015

MedVantx, Inc - San Diego, CA

- Designed complex HL7 interfaces to support various EMR/EHR vendors like,
  eClinicalWorks, NextGen, Allscripts, Epic, AthenaHealth, GE Centricity and Aprima
- Created and monitored HL7 connections using Mirth Connect
- Served as Mirth Appliance administrator
- Modified proprietary java program to parse and manipulate HL7 data
- Salesforce administration duties
- Troubleshoot and resolved HL7 interface issues escalated from customer support and other departments with a high success rate
- Worked with customer service and sales executives on development and design of EMR/EHR HL7 interfaces
- Served as database administrator for Sybase running on Linux systems
- Developed and manage HL7 project plans while providing status updates to management
- Developed and maintain accurate network documentation and Visio diagrams to provide management with proper understanding of organizational needs
- Created project plans that analyze system gaps and build reasonable timeline Negotiate costs for interfaces from EMR/EHR vendors
- Managed multiple inbound and outbound EMR interfaces using Mirth
- Created and maintain shell scripts in Linux
- · Served as Salesforce administrator
- Worked with proprietary Java program to map HL7 data (ADT, SIU) Pharmacy messaging, (RDS, RDE)
- Built/created virtual machine images Yearly HIPAA and security trainings
- Designed interfaces to post or update to patient medical record
- Built reusable code applied to other projects, effectively saving company \$500 dollars in consulting fees and twenty development hours
- Established go-live process by
- Defined and conducted design processes at all stages, including research, conceptualization, testing and implementation
- Designed site layouts and user interfaces using web services integration and Mirth Connect
- Translated concepts into user flows, wireframes, mockups and prototypes to promote positive intuitive designs, site interactions and user experiences
- Completed design projects to meet budget, equipment, performance and legal requirements
- Gathered, defined and translated client requirements into product stories and actionable tasks
- Coded user-customizable applications to convert raw data from design engine to easily understandable graphical formats
- Participated in pre-project analysis and technical assessments to develop userfriendly interface and correct functionality to meet business objectives
- Maintained strong education in latest technologies, software and hardware products for use in various projects

- Designed complex HL7 interfaces to support EMR systems for eClinicalWorks, GE Centricity, Allscripts, and NextGen for various Health Information Exchanges Worked with Lab, Radiology and Transcription HL7 data (ORU, ORM, MDM)
- Used XSLT to parse and manipulate HL7 data Worked with LOINC coding and SNOMED codes in design of bi-directional HL7 interfaces
- Worked with clients to analyze computing and network needs and installed appropriate solutions within each organization's budget
- Executed and monitored standards for HL7 user interfaces, page design and graphics development
- Served as operating system expert, providing technical support for entire organization
- Created and maintained inbound and outbound EMR interfaces using Mirth Mentored and trained new employees Resolved production and deployment issues by researching problems and developing solutions
- Facilitated conference calls with customer and other related departments to complete project in timely manner

### **Systems Analyst**

May 2006 to Nov 2009

Skylight Healthcare Systems - San Diego, CA

- Worked on HL7 integration projects for Meditech, Cerner, Siemens, Allscripts, Epic and various other third party clinical applications for multiple hospital facilities
- Managed multiple inbound and outbound HL7 EMR interfaces using Interfaceware (Iguana and Chameleon)
- Facilitated conference calls with various customers and affiliates to successfully complete HL7 projects
- Implemented project activities for HL7 inbound/outbound interfaces
- Used Python to manipulate HL7 data
- · Visited customer facilities to troubleshoot system
- Built Red Hat rack mounted servers ready for field installation
- Provided support to field staff
- Worked directly with healthcare staff
- Installed and configured SQL Server
- Worked in blended environment of Linux and Windows
- Created shell scripts in Linux.

Create and design Action Lists based on client's specifications

## Education

#### Master of Arts, Telecommunications

San Diego State University - San Diego, US

Completed coursework in Telecommunications and Film. Completed and defended film thesis.

#### Bachelor of Arts, Communication

University of California - San Diego, CA, US Major in Communication

# Skill Highlights

- Salesforce Administration
- Write SQL Queries
- Java Programming
- Linux administration
- Strong collaborative skills
- Interfaceware Interface Engine
- Python Programming
- Excellent problem solving skills
- HL7 data structures 2,x
- Windows patch management

- Technical helpdesk experience
- Linux shell scripting
- TCP/IP protocols
- · Information security
- Java script
- SQL Server querying
- · Active Directory administration
- Dynamics GP Administration
- StarLIMS Administration
- FHIR Training
- HIPAA Training

# **Summary**

Experienced Health Integration Analyst with thirteen years of experience in the healthcare information space. Specialties include building strong client relationships, building and designing HL7 interface connections and troubleshooting and resolving production issues. A key change leader recognized for frequent smiling and being a collaborative and helpful team player to achieve operational efficiency, drive revenue and build morale.